<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Darren</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Darren</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Hong Kong&#39;s Airbnb Market</title>
      <link>/blogs/air_bnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/air_bnb/</guid>
      <description>For our final group project, we looked into Airbnbs in Hong Kong and tried to create a regression model to predict the price for 4 nights for two people at an Airbnb. I am originally from Hong Kong, so this analyis was enlightening and fun at the same time as I got to understand more about Hong Kong’s Airbnb market and how different varibles would affect prices.
For this section, let’s look deeper into Hong Kong’s Airbnb data!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Movies - IMDB Dataset</title>
      <link>/blogs/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/movies/</guid>
      <description>Movies One of my absolute favourite things to do during my pastime is to sit down with my family and friends on a couch and put on a visually mesmerizing, thought provoking movie, with beer and popcorn flowing of course. Thus, I am extremely interested in analyzing movies and understanding all the different factors that come into play in the movie industry. Here, we will look in detail into the different genres of movies from IMDB, and analyze key figures such as their budget, ratings and gross earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change</title>
      <link>/blogs/climate_change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/climate_change/</guid>
      <description>Climate Change is the defining issue of our time and we are at the defining moment of our lives. The scope of the impacts of climate change are global and unprecedented in scale and it is our duty to take drastic action today to do as much as we can to protect our environment and keep our planet healthy.
Climate Change: What does the data say? To this day, there are still many that deny the effect of climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yield Curve Analysis</title>
      <link>/blogs/yieldcurve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/yieldcurve/</guid>
      <description>The Yield Curve The Yield Curve is simply the difference between short and long-term interest rates. It is important in the world of finance not only because it is used as a benchmark for other debt in the market, such as mortgages or bank lending rates, but also because it can be used to predict changes in economic output and overall growth. Here, we will download and attempt to analyze historical US yield rates of diffent maturities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
